Infuriating!
This is absolutely vexing!
Majesty, you're covered in filth.
What happened to you?
Moreover, where are all the others?
Damn fools.
Why did I bother giving them high caliber
weaponry if they don't know how to use it?
Majesty, what in heaven is that?
Now that's impossible.
The dragon of calamity.
What is this?
The Brio-Lak should have destroyed it!
Could it perhaps?
Was it resurrected somehow?
Impossible. No way.
They do have that damn cleric.
That infernal healer who can use his
magic far beyond anyone else. Sane.
But even if he did heal it,
it would be impossible for them
to just sick that dragon on me.
Someone must be controlling it.
Demon folk.
Where is our monster person? Pardon?
Where is the Beast Tabor?
Yes, of course, Master Lude.
He has already left for Sorenza.
He spoke of urgent business there.
Of course, that damned Quisling.
Change sides, Azzy.
Why did you not try to detain him?
Your Majesty, you told us to give
him special treatment, so I...
My liege, please compose yourself.
I suggest you stop standing around like an
ass and come up with a plan to fix this,
damned good fun of things!
Yes, sire.
Now, get the device ready! The device?
I'm not sure which one you mean.
The Koraunos, of course.
The Koraunos?
And be quick about it!
Um, with all due respect, sir, the
Koraunos weapon is still in testing.
Output remains too high and the
sights are unpredictable at best.
And it is wildly dangerous to use
within the city, you wretched coward!
Do you not see the disaster
that is right in front of you?
Yes I do.
But the risk of massive
collateral damage is now.
Do it.
We only need one shot.
That is all.
It will take to kill it.
And if you cannot aim it
properly and implement
mana tracing on the gun barrel
right as you command? Sir.
You mindless abomination.
I'm going to blow you out
of the sky without a trace!
Acquiring target, direction 1120.
Angle of fire, 40 degrees.
Mana tracing applied.
Behold the greatest technological
wonder in the Empire!
Developed under the wise leadership
of Doradus III, the Light of Judgment!
Peri!
Your Majesty,
the trajectory of Karanos has been
altered and now it's raining down on us!
Talk to me!
How did that happen?
The beam was programmed to trace mana!
It's now targeting our mana furnaces!
Why would you ever use
something like that?
Have you no sense at all?
We're all done for!
I'm getting off this merry-go-round!
You are in charge now!
That's a direct order!
Where are you going?
You do something.
That is an order from
your direct superior.
It's for the pleasure, sir!
You cowards!
I'll have your heads for this!
Please, no, not those!
Anything but those!
Not my babies!
This can't be happening!
Breaking stuff!
Let's go to the world.
If you look at me, I'm
going to go to the world.
If you look at me, I can't give up.
What do you want?
Thank you so much for watching.
I'm sorry but I seem to
have lost track of him.
I'm trying to pinpoint him but it's as if
there's something
preventing me from doing so.
Then he must be in a
building made of monometal.
Instructor Noor!
Instructor!
Oh!
Um, something's coming.
It's brighter than the light from before!
Fly out of the way!
There's no time!
Everyone, get behind me now!
Instructor!
Perry!
Quill got it!
Instructor!
What do you think you're doing?
You were the one who ordered me to come
up with a way to fix this, my liege.
Damn, Tregers.
You do realize this is
treason against the crown?
It is the only way we can
ensure the Empire survive.
No, no, don't.
Someone help me. Seize them.
There is no one here who is
still willing to obey you.
Reap what you sow.
Wow.
Well, that was lucky.
The sparkly gold old guy.
And who the hell are you?
Do you mean to protect this man? No.
Then you need to stay out of our way.
I'm not sure what's going
on, but let's calm down.
Harry!
Old-timer, stay low.
What are you attacking me for?
This man is a seasoned bodyguard.
We must charge together.
This is a misunderstanding.
I see no other way to interpret this
than what is right in front of me!
Perry!
That man has brought irreparable
harm upon our country,
and he must atone for
it with his very life.
I see you guys have some issues,
but can't you just talk it out?
Were that possible, we'd have done it!
Is that a bomb?
Watch out!
Why are you all ganging
up on him like this?
He's just an old man.
You're the one who sent him flying.
Okay, yeah, but isn't he supposed to
be, like, your big emperor or something?
This is all really confusing to me.
That's fine.
You don't need to understand.
Huh? I gotcha.
Could you knock it off?
What is this?
What are you doing?
Do you think you can
just kill him yourself?
Of course I'm not going to kill him.
This guy's super old.
He'll probably die any day now.
Let nature do its thing.
We do not have a single moment to spare.
Our enemies are invading our territory.
And they have the Dragon
of Calamity with them.
Who's invading?
We need to show them that we have
absolutely no intention of fighting.
Our country is doomed unless
we offer them his head.
It is for our survival.
Wait right there.
We appreciate your thoughtfulness,
but there will be no need for that.
For dead men cannot suffer while
they atone for their crimes.
You guys made it.
That's great.
Thanks to you.
And you made it. Yeah.
I thought I was going to eat
it, but I really lucked out.
Are they who I think they are?
Surnar, if you would please, allow
us to take care of things from here.
They're pretty riled up, but I've
been trying to talk them down.
Why don't you try giving it a shot?
They won't listen to me.
Thank you.
Lin, could you go with Sir
Noor to tend to his wounds?
Come on, then.
Let's get you patched up. Right.
Good luck sorting it out.
Now, then.
It has been quite a while since we
last encountered you. Prince Rain!
Please lower your weapons, gentlemen.
and before anything, we would like
to have a discussion with this man.
Please, spare my life.
You want to live?
Are you telling me that you
want to receive compassion?
Sure.
I fully intend to forgive you.
Yes? Really? Then I...
There are 23 people in our nation.
Who are missing?
19 people have been buried
under crumbling homes.
13 have been burned to death in fires.
38 people injured by falling debris.
Furthermore, there are
people who were torn apart,
crushed, and reduced to
mangled pieces of flesh?
by the beasts you unleashed.
There are 127 of those.
That total is the number of
casualties in my country.
Although I'm certain that
more will be discovered.
Uh, why are you telling me all this?
Because as I said earlier,
I will forgive you.
But only after you have
experienced the same amount
of suffering as all those
people I just mentioned,
yes?
Only then will we hold talks about
reparations and ending the war.
What say you?
Are there objections?
No objections.
No, wait, please.
You cannot go through with this.
There must be some other way.
No need to worry.
You'll experience their
pain, but you won't die.
Even if we tear off both your
legs and pulverize your innards,
I shall make sure you are
healed enough to survive it.
At least enough to talk to us.
Someone help me!
Even if you cannot handle it
and you lose consciousness,
we'll just bring you back again.
Feel free to cry and
scream as much as you like.
Please, I beg you!
Don't get me wrong, Emperor.
However, we're not doing this
because we want to relish in it.
What we do want though
is for you to thoroughly
understand the pain that you
have put our people through.
That's it.
And then you can consider
yourself forgiven.
Because our nation is incredibly
merciful, don't you think?
Ah, thank you.
You are so good at healing stuff.
Ah, thank you. I try.
So much damage.
Did that light from earlier do this?
Yes, it did.
The mana beam that you
deflected was split apart and
then started raining down
on the Imperial Capital.
Oh no, didn't mean for that to happen.
Don't let it bother you, Instructor.
You only did it to protect us
and the good of the nation.
Yeah, well, that may be true, but
I didn't want anyone to get hurt.
Oh, no, you don't have
to worry about that.
Apparently, the facilities that
got destroyed were mana furnaces.
Mana furnaces? Yes.
Those areas have a very
high concentration of mana,
so people aren't able to enter them.
Oh, yeah?
Then that's good, I guess.
But of course, it will still affect
the lives of the citizens here.
But not so much that they
can't recover from it.
Brother!
Ben, it's all over now, right? Yes, it is.
And we're all moving towards
coordinating post-war reconstruction.
Wait, the war barely started and now
you're telling us that it's already over?
Now I really don't understand why we just
didn't talk it out from the beginning.
So, uh, what about the old fella?
The emperor guy?
He chose to step down
and abdicate the throne.
It is most likely his grandchild will
be chosen to inherit the crown next.
Like a little kid?
They are but ten years old at this point,
which means that a guardian
has to be appointed.
From the ten you met earlier.
Those guys are gonna do it?
Sir Noor, do I have your name right? Yeah.
I apologize for before.
I misunderstood the situation
when we turned our blades on you.
I will do whatever it
takes to make amends.
I'm not really worried about
it, so no need for all that.
But please, ganging up on
the elderly is kind of wrong.
You should check your principles.
Right, that is something to be ashamed of.
And had you not been there to
stop us from going further,
our empire would have certainly
ended up in a very nasty civil war.
So I would like to thank you for that.
No, it's okay.
I really don't deserve any thanks.
In fact, I'm really the one who got saved.
I thought I was a goner when I
stupidly jumped off the dragon.
But luckily, you guys had a floor
right there to break my fall.
Okay, friend, whatever you call it.
Yes, you truly are an amusing man.
It is an honor and a
pleasure to have met you.
And please, you need to know.
From this moment on, the Ten will
spare no expense to assist you.
So if you ever need our
help, just say the word.
We will risk our lives
to come to your aid.
Wow, that's a bit heavy on the
dramatics, but I'll be fine.
Do not hesitate to ask.
Anyways, guys, sorry I got
your city all messed up.
Instructor Noor.
Do not concern yourself with that.
As of right now, there have been
no reports of any dead or injured.
The crimes committed by our country,
which threw away the treaty
and attacked your nation,
are far more serious.
Okay, sure, but please let me
know what I can do to help out.
I can at least drag
out some of the rubble.
You're ridiculous.
Such a good-hearted
person to a fault I say
it said it's bored and
wants to go home that?
Okay!
I bid you farewell from now on we will
correspond through messengers yes please
return home safely I almost forgot sir
no forgive me I I never shared my name.
I am Imperial Sorcerer Sir
Randeus, of the Circuit of Ten.
Okay. Rand...
It's Randy, right?
I'll remember, Randall.
I do look forward to seeing
you once again someday.
Same, Ricky.
Right. We're off.
Rolo, can you ask it
something for me? Huh?
On the way home, can we fly a
little closer to the ground?
Sure, I'll ask it.
I can see how deeply concerned he is
about the damage done to this nation.
What a compassionate person he is!
I must learn from his example.
Father, we have all returned safely.
I can report the war is now over.
I would like for you
to do the negotiating.
You can fill me in on all the
details later this evening,
and now I must extend
thanks to our Savior.
Yes.
Sir Noor made incredible
contributions on the field.
He needs a reward worthy of his deeds.
Oh no, come on.
That's not necessary. Pardon me?
Sir, I'm flattered by the offer, but
I don't really need anything, okay?
No, no, you cannot blow it
off and refuse me this time.
I need to provide you
with the proper reward or
else it will set a poor
example for everybody else.
Yeah, I get all that, but, man,
this family, they are so pushy.
Even after you tell them
you don't want anything.
Um, actually, there is one thing
I'd like to ask for. Oh, really?
Ah, yes, of course.
Go ahead, just name it, anything.
So, uh, I would like for
you to help this kid out.
Huh? Help me? But why?
This child is demon folk, yes?
He is, and he doesn't
have anyone to live with.
Because he was abandoned by
a group of slave merchants.
All right, then.
What might be your request for the boy?
He could live in the capital.
He just needs a normal life.
You know, just like all the
other people living there.
I would have him live with me,
but it would probably be better for him
if he were with a family with some money.
Not a guy like me, with no real income.
Oh, Instructor Noor.
At one point, you said you'd
give me a house and land.
Something like that
would be great for him.
And some clothes and food if you can.
Very well, then.
But in order for that to happen,
he must first become a lawful
citizen of this kingdom.
Is that what you wish for him, Sonor?
He has saved me several times
throughout our journey together.
And the only reason that huge dragon did
what it did was because Rolo was there.
That's not true!
It was because you were a -
There's no need to be humble now.
If Rolo weren't there, the war
would not have ended so quickly.
He deserves it, Your Highness.
Of all the things he could request,
the holy theocracy of Mithra
regards the demon-focused enemies.
Accepting one into our kingdom
will cause a rift in our relations.
And please believe me, I don't
need anything other than that.
If you still want to give out some
rewards, then do that for someone else.
There is no shortage of people
who lost everything in this.
That's really where we should be focusing
all our efforts right now anyway.
Yes, you're exactly right.
Matter of fact, I'm wondering
who's the king here.
This guy really does like to laugh.
If I'm to be reborn,
I only hope I won't have to spend
that life with so much suffering.
I hope I can be at least a
little more useful to someone.
And I hope I can have something
delicious to eat at least once.
Life doesn't have to be this way.
For the time being, you
will be living here with me.
So welcome home, Rolo
Something wrong?
They made a nice meal for us, but it'll
get cold if you don't go ahead and eat
What, I can eat all this?
Of course you can eat it.
This is our dinner.
Or is it something that
you don't really like?
This is real food
Eat don't be shy Rolo everything's
fine have as much as you want
no one will be upset with you
okay then I'll try some thank you
the pretzel soft and fluffy
What is it?
It's delicious.
You can slow down, Rolo.
No one will take it away.
I believe that I have believed in the
miracle of my
dreams What
can
I do?
What can I do?
I have left my heart.
The moment I wanna hear you...
But now I will not
be able to hear you...
I can't hear you...
But I don't want to hear you.
I don't want to hear you...
Thank you.